Michael mss. LMC 2996
Lilly Library
- Playbills
  - Hay Fever; George Bernard Shaw; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Heidi Chronicles, The; Wendy Wasserstein; Plymouth Theatre, 1990; 2 Copies (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Heiress, The; R. & A. Goetz; Walter Kerr Theatre, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hello, Dolly!; Stewart, Herman; Orpheum, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hello, Dolly!; Stewart, Herman; IU Auditorium, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Henceforward; Alan Ayckbourn; Vaudeville Theatre, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Henry V; William Shakespeare; Drame SNG Ljiblijana, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Henry V; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Henry VI, Part I; William Shakespeare; Wurttembergishche Staatth'r, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Herbal Bed, The; Peter Whelan; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - High Society; Kopit, Porter; Festival Theatre, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - His Majesty; Harley Granville Barker; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - History Boys, The; Alan Bennett; Studio Theatre, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - History of Vasco, The; Georges Schehade; Toneelgroep Theater, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Holmes and Watson; Jeffrey Hatcher; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Home and Beauty; Somerset Maugham; Lyric Theatre, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Homecoming, The; Harold Pinter; Music Box, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hostage, The; Brendan Behan; Theatre Royal Stratford, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hot L Baltimore, The; Lanford Wilson; Circle in the Square Theatre, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hot Summer Night; Ted Willis; Bristol Hippodrome, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - House of Atreus, The; Aeschylus; Tyrone Guthrie Theatre, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hunger and Thirst; Eugene Ionesco; Drama Theatre, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - I Ought to Be in Pictures; Neil Simon; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ideal Husband, An; Oscar Wilde; Lyric Theatre, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ideal Wife, The; Marco Praga; Piccolo Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - If/Then; Kitt & Yorkey; Richard Rodgers Theatre, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Illusionists, The; Basso, Blaque, etc.; IU Auditorium, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Imaginary Friends; Nora Ephron; Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 2002; 2 Copies (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Imaginary Invalid, The; Moliere; Landestheater Linz, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, The; Oscar Wilde; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, The; Oscar Wilde; Avon Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, The; Oscar Wilde; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Importance of Being Earnest, The; Oscar Wilde; Avon Theatre, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - In Celebration; David Storey; Royal Court Theatre, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - In The Heights; Miranda, Hudes; Richard Rodgers Theatre, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Inadmissable Evidence; John Osborne; Belasco Theatre, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Incorruptible; Michael Hollinger; Theatre in the Square (GA), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Indian Ink; Tom Stoppard; Aldwych Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Inherit the Wind; Lawrence, Lee; Waldron Auditorium, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Inspector Calls, An; J.B. Priestley; Aldwych Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Invention of Love, The; Tom Stoppard; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Invention of Love, The; Tom Stoppard; Studio Theatre (Chicago), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Irish Play, The; Ron Hutchinson; Donmar Warehouse, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Irma La Douce; Monnot, Breffort; Lyric Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - It's Only a Play; Terrance McNally; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ivanov; Anton Chekhov; Vivian Beaumont Theater, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jasper Station; Thomas, Foster; Thousand Islands Playhouse, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jelly's Last Jam; Wolfe, Morton, Birkenhead; Virginia Theatre, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jersey Boys; Brickman, Elice, Gaudio, etc.; Clowes Hall, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jerusalem; Zez Butterworth; The Music Box, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jim and Jill; Grey, Newman, Ellis; Die Kleine Komodie, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Jitney; August Wilson; Goodman Theatre, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Joe Egg; Peter Nichols; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - John Gabriel Borkman; Henrik Ibsen; Circle in the Square Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Jorrocks; Cross, Heneker; New Theatre, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat; Webber, Rice; Royale Theatre, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat; Webber, Rice; IU Auditorium, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Jubilee; Tazewell Thompson; Arena Stage, 2019 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Juno and the Paycock; Sean O'Casey; Det Kongelige Teater, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Juno and the Paycock; Sean O'Casey; Aldwych Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Juno and the Paycock; Sean O'Casey; Irish Repertory Theatre, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Kafka's Dick; Alan Bennett; Picadilly Theatre, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Katydid, The; Michael Davis Sutton; Phoenix Theatre, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King and I, The; Rodgers, Hammerstein; Malmo Stadsteater, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King Hirsch; Otto Zoff; Bayerische Staatschauspiel, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King Lear; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King Lear; William Shakespeare; Chicago Shakespeare Theater, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King Lear; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - King Lear; Tskikurishvili, Cunis; Synetic Theater (Washington), 2011 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Kinky Boots; Fierstein, Lauper; Clowes Hall, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman; McNally, Kander, Ebb; Broadhurst Theatre, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Knack, The; Jellicoe; The New Theatre (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Krasnoyarsk Cultural Dance; IU Auditorium, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Kreig Mit den Molchen, Der; Karel Capek; Stadtische Buhnen Dortmond, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - La Cage Aux Folles; Herman, Fierstein; Golden Gate Theatre, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - La Plume de Ma Tante; Robert Dhery; St. Paul Auditorium, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Landscape; Harold Pinter; Lyttelton Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Lark, The; Lillian Hellman; Longacre Theatre, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Last of Mrs. Cheyney, The; Frederick Lonsdale; Cambridge Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Later Life; A.R. Gurney; Westside Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Laughing Matter, A; April DeAngelis; Lyttelton Theatre, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Laughter on the 23rd Floor; Neil Simon; Richard Rodgers Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Les Choutes; Barillet, Gredy; Theatre des Noveautes, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Les Liaisons Dangereuses; Christopher Hamptom; Pit Theatre, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Les Miserables; Boubil, Schonberg; Palace Theatre, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Les Miserables; Boubil, Schonberg; IU Auditorium, 2020 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Lesson From Aloes, A; Athol Fugard; Playhouse Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Lettice and Lovage; Peter Shaffer; Globe Theatre Shaftesbury, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Life, A; Hugh Leonard; Morosco Theatre, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Life of Galileo; Bertolt Brecht; Berliner Ensemble, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Life x3; Yasmina Reza; Lyttelton Theatre, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Lion King, The; John, Rice; New Amsterdam Theatre, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Little Foxes, The; Lillian Hellman; Theatre in Wandsbek, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Mary Sunshine; Rick Besoyan; Players Theatre, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Night Music, A; Sondheim, Wheeler; Shubert Theatre, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Night Music, A; Sondheim, Wheeler; Starlight Musicals, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Night Music, A; Sondheim, Wheeler; Oliver Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Night Music, A; Sondheim, Wheeler; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Shop of Horrors; Ashman, Menken; Orpheum Theatre, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Little Shop of Horrors; Ashman, Menken; Cardinal Stage Company, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Lock Up Your Daughters; Miles, Johnson, Bart; Mermaid Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - London Assurance; Dion Boucicault; Avon Theatre, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Long and the Short and the Tall; Willis Hall; Royal Court Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Long Christmas Ride Home; Paula Vogel; Vineyard Theatre, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Long Day's Journey Into Night; Eugene O'Neill; Lyric Theatre, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Look After Lulu!; Noel Coward; Royal Court Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Loot; Joe Orton; Arts Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Lost in Yonkers; Neil Simon; Richard Rodgers Theatre, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Love for Love; William Congreve; Lyttelton Theatre, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Love List, The; Norm Foster; Thousand Islands Playhouse, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Love! Valor! Compassion!; Terrence McNally; Walter Kerr Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Lupone, Patti, and Mandy Patinkin; Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Luther; John Osborne; St. James Theatre, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - M. Butterfly; David Henry Hwang; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Macbeth; William Shakespeare; Vokstheater, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Macbeth; William Shakespeare; Royal Court Theatre, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Macbeth; William Shakespeare; Barbican Theatre, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Macbeth; William Shakespeare; Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Macbeth; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Machinal; Sophie Treadwell; Lyttelton Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Madame Melville; Richard Nelson; Vaudeville Theatre, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Madness of George III, The; Alan Bennett; Lyttelton Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Maid of Orleans, The; Freidrich Schiller; Burgtheater, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Make and Break; Michael Frayn; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Malcontent, The; John Marston; Gielgud Theatre, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mamma Mia!; Anderson, Ulvaeus; IU Auditorium, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Man and Superman; George Bernard Shaw; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Man For All Seasons, A; Robert Bolt; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 1998; 2 Copies (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Man for All Seasons, A; Robert Bolt; ANTA Theatre, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Man of La Mancha; Dale Wasserman; ANTA Washington Square, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Man of La Mancha; Dale Wasserman; Martin Beck Theatre, 2002; 2 Copies (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Maria Stuart; Freidrich Schiller; Landestheater Salzburg, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Mary Stuart; Friedrich Schiller; Old Vic Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Mary Stuart; Friedrich Schiller; Theatre in the Square (GA), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Mary Mary; Jean Kerr; Komodie Basel, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Master Builder, The; Henrik Ibsen; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Master Class; Terrence McNally; John Golden Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Master Harold and the Boys; Athol Fugard; Lyceum Theatre, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Matilda; Kelly, Minchin; Shubert Theatre, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Mauritius; Theresa Rebeck; Biltmore Theatre, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Me and My Girl; Rose, Furber, Gay; Adelphi Theatre, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Measure for Measure; William Shakespeare; Kungl. Dramatisksa Teatern, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Measure for Measure; William Shakespeare; Berliner Ensemble, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Medea; Euripides; Wyndham's Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Melons; Bernard Pomerance; Pit Theatre, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Memory House; Kathleen Tolan; Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Menopause the Musical; Jeanie Linders; Beef & Boards Dinner Theatre, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Merchant of Venice; William Shakespeare; Barbican Theatre, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Merchant of Venice; William Shakespeare; 46th Street Theatre, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Merrily We Roll Along; Sondheim, Furth; Donmar, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor; William Shakespeare; Schauspielhaus Bochum, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor; William Shakespeare; Teatro Eliseo, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Meteor, The; Friedrich Durrenmatt; Aldwych Theatre, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream; William Shakespeare; Wuppertaler Buhnen, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Miracle Worker, The; William Gibson; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Miraculous Night, A; Slawomir Mrozek; Studio de Brakke Grond, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Miser, The; Moliere; Freie Volksbuhne, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Miss Saigon; Boubil, Schonberg; Auditorium Theatre Chicago, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Miss Witherspoon; Christopher Durang; Playwrights Horizons, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Mithridate; Jean Racine; Comedie Francaise, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Molly Sweeney; Brian Friel; Steppenwolf, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Moon for the Misbegotten, A; Eugene O'Neill; Teatro Eleanora Duse (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Moon Over Buffalo; Ken Ludwig; Martin Beck Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Moonlight; Harold Pinter; Comedy Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Moot the Messenger; Kia Corthron; Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Morning's At Seven; Paul Osborn; Lyceum Theatre, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Morning's At Seven; Paul Osborn; Arcade Theatre (Florida), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mother Courage and Her Children; Bertolt Brecht; Martin Beck Theatre, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mother Courage and Her Children; Bertolt Brecht; Cottesloe Theatre, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mother Courage and Her Children; Bertolt Brecht; Oliver Theatre, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mousetrap, The; Agatha Christie; St. Martin's Theatre, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Movin' Out; Billy Joel, Twyla Tharp; IU Auditorium, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mrs. Klein; Nicholas Wright; Apollo Theatre, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession; George Bernard Shaw; Lyttelton Theatre, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession; George Bernard Shaw; Strand Theatre, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession; George Bernard Shaw; American Airline Theatre, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Much Ado About Nothing; William Shakespeare; Schiller-Theater, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Much Ado About Nothing; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Much Ado About Nothing; William Shakespeare; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Much Ado About Nothing; William Shakespeare; Avon Theatre, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Much Ado About Nothing; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Murderers; Jeffrey Hatcher; Studio Two, Riffe Center, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - My Name is Asher Lev; Aaron Posner; West Side Theatre/Upstairs, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Mystery of Charles Dickens, The; Peter Ackroyd; Albery Theatre, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Narrow Road to the Deep North; Edward Bond; Mitzie E. Newhouse Theatre, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Nest, The; Bathsheba Doran; Signature Theatre, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Next to Normal; Kit, Yorkey; Cardinal Stage Company, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - New Electric Ballroom, The; Edna Walsh; Studio Theatre, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Nice Work If You Can Get It; Girshwins, DiPietro; IU Auditorium, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Nicholas Nickleby; Charles Dickens; Aldwich Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 'night, Mother; Marsha Norman; John Golden Theatre, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - No Limits to Love; David Mercer; Donmar Warehouse, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - No Man's Land; Harold Pinter; Longacre Theatre, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - No Man's Land; Harold Pinter; Cort Theatre, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - No, No, Nanette; Youmans, Harbach; 46th Street Theatre, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Noises Off; Michael Frayn; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Noises Off; Michael Frayn; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Noises Off; Michael Frayn; Lyttelton Theatre, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Noises Off; Michael Frayn; Avon Theatre, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Not Quite Jerusalem; Paul Kember; Royal Court Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Number, A; Caryl Churchill; New York Theatre Workshop, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Odd Couple, The; Neil Simon; Plymouth Theatre, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Old Neighborhood, The; David Mamet; Booth Theatre, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Old Times; Harold Pinter; Billy Rose Theatre, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Oleanna; David Mamet; Orpheum Theatre, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Oliver!; Lionel Bart; St. Paul Auditorium, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Oliver!; Lionel Bart; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2006 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - On the Razzle; Tom Stoppard; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - On the 20th Century; Comden & Green; American Airline Theatre, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Once; Walsh, Hansard, Irglova; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Only Kidding; Jim Geoghan; Wisdom Bridge Theatre, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Onward Victoria; Anker, Herman; Martin Beck Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Orpheus Descending; Tennessee Williams; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Othello; William Shakespeare; Bayerische Staatstheater, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Othello; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Othello; William Shakespeare; Barbican Theatre, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Othello; William Shakespeare; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Other Desert Cities; Jon Robin Baitz; Booth Theatre, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Other People's Money; Jerry Sterner; Minetta Lane Theatre, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Other Place, The; Sharr White; Samuel J. Friedman Theatre, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Pacific Overtures; Stephen Sondheim; Studio 54, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Pal Joey; Rogers, Hart, O'Hara; Albery Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Pal Joey; Rogers, Hart, O'Hara; Royal George Theatre (Niagara), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Panoptikum; Ferenc Molnar; Theater in der Josefstadt, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Parade; Uhry, Brown; Vivian Beaumont Theater, 1998; 2 Copies (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Party, The; Jane Arden; New Theatre, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Passion, The; Cottesloe Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Passion, The; Peter Nichols; Longacre Theatre, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Passion; Sondheim, Lapine; Plymouth Theatre, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Patience; Gilbert & Sullivan; Oxford Playhouse, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Pecong; Steve Carter; Victory Gardens Theater, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Pericles; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959; 2 Copies (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Persecution and Assassination of Marat as Performed by the Inmates of the Asylum of Charenton Under the Direction of the Marquis de Sade; Peter Weiss; Martin Beck Theatre, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Persians, The; Aeschylus; Stadtische Buhnen Munster, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Peter Pan; J.M. Barrie; Oliver Theatre, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Peter Pan (Musical); J.M. Barrie et al.; Cardinal Stage Company, 2017 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Peter and the Star Catcher; Rick Elice; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Peters, Bernadette; IU Auditorium, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Phantom of the Opera; Webber, Hart; Her Majesty's Theatre, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Phedre; Jean Racine; Deutsches Schauspielhaus, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Phedre; Jean Racine; Tom Patterson Theatre, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Phillip Hotz's Fury; Eugene Ionesco; Contra Kreis Theater, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Piece of My Heart, A; Shirley Lauro; Actors Theatre of Louisville, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pillowman, The; Martin McDonagh; Studio Theatre, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pippin; Hirson, Schwartz; Imperial Theatre, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pippin; Hirson, Schwartz; IU Auditorium, 2017 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pitmen Painters, The; Lee Hall; Samuel J. Friedman Theatre, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Platonov; Anton Chekhov; Akademietheater, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Play About the Baby, The; Edward Albee; Studio Theatre, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Play, Orchestra, Play; Noel Coward; Royal George Theater (Niagara), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Play What I Wrote, The; McColl, Foley, Braben; Wyndham's Theatre, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Playboy of the Western World, The; J.M. Synge; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Potting Shed, The; Graham Green; Little Theatre Bristol, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Prelude to a Kiss; Craig Lucas; Helen Hayes Theatre, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Prescription: Murder; Link, Levinson; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, The; Jay Presson Allen; Wyndham's Theatre, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Private Ear and the Public Eye, The; Peter Shaffer; Morosco Theatre, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Private Lives; Noel Coward; Duchess Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Producers, The; Mel Brooks; St. James Theatre, 2002; 2 Copies (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Producers, The; Mel Brooks; IU Auditorium, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Proof; David Auburn; Walter Kerr Theatre, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Proposals; Neil Simon; Broadhurst Theatre, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Provok'd Wife, The; John Vanbrugh; Lyttleton Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Ragtime; McNally, Flaherty; Aherns; Ford Center for the Performing Arts, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Raisin; Nemiroff, Woldin, Brittan; Arena Stage, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Raisin in the Sun, A; Lorraine Hansberry; Bristol Hippodrome, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Rattle of a Simple Man; Charles Dyer; Savoy Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Real Inspector Hound / The Critic; Stoppard / Sheridan; Oliver Theatre, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Real Thing, The; Tom Stoppard; Plymouth Theatre, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Reasons To Be Pretty; Neil LaBute; Studio Theatre, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Rehearsal, The; Jean Anouilh; Royale Theatre, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Relative Values; Noel Coward; Savoy Theatre, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Reluctant Debutante, The; William Douglas Home; Theatre Royal Bath, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rent; Jonathan Larson; Nederlander Theatre, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rent; Jonathan Larson; IU Auditorium, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Retreat from Moscow, The; William Nicholson; Booth Theatre, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Reversible; Gypsy Snider; IU Auditorium, 2019 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rhinoceros; Ionesco; Strand Theatre, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rhinoceros; Ionesco; Longacre Theatre, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Richard II; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Richard II; William Shakespeare; Phoenix Theatre London, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Richard II; William Shakespeare; Cottesloe Theatre, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Richard III; William Shakespeare; Avon Theatre, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Rink, The; McNally, Kander, Ebb; Signature Theatre, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 58)